fishgame3d.com 2019-04-24

# AquaLife 3D

**Privacy Policy**

This privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") describes what information Gladiators Software ("Developer" or "We") collects, uses, and shares your personal information while you play our mobile application ("Mobile App") and/or use Gladiators Software website that link to this Privacy Policy ("Website"). We refer to our Mobile App users as users ("Users").

We may make changes to this Privacy Policy from time to time. These updates, will take effect from the date of issue on our website at fishgame3d.com. Please, check back regularly for the updates.

What kind of personal information does Gladiators Software collect?

We aim to minimize how much personal information we collect from users when they play the Mobile App or use the Website. We collect the personal information that you voluntarily provide to us (e.g. email addresses when you contact our customer support team directly from Mobile App), but most of our data collection is limited to the following types of data, which do not identify you personally (e.g.game play information). In some countries, this type of data may be considered as personal information:

Personal Information  
Information from Connected Social Network Accounts.  
You may connect your Mobile App account to your Facebook or VK account so that you can keep up with your friends' progress as they play the Mobile App. We will collect which of your friends on Facebook or VK are also playing the Mobile App.

Name and email address  
You have the option to contact our customer support team directly from our Mobile App. When you do, we will collect and use this information to respond to your requests and/or comments.  
If you contact our customer team, whether via email or by filling out a contact form on the Website, we will collect and use this information to respond to your requests and/or comments.

Does Gladiators Software Collect My Financial Information When I Make In-App Purchases?

When you make in-app purchases in the Mobile App, we do not collect or have any access to your name and billing information. This information is collected and stored by your platform (e.g. Apple's Game Store or Android's Google Play) or your platform's payment processor.

Do third parties have access to my personal information?

We do not sell or share Personal Information with any third parties or other companies for marketing purposes. We have the right to provide any and all personal information to law enforcement agencies, regulators, government agencies, the court in order to comply with the applicable law, to respond to their legitimate requests.

How long will Gladiators Software keep my personal information?

How long we store your personal information will depend on the purpose that we originally collected it. We will not retain personal information for longer than is necessary for our business or for legal requirements. You may request deletion at any time of all data by contacting our customer support team directly from our Mobile App. The data will be deleted 7 days after the request, provided there is no activity in the Mobile App.

Cookies and similar tracking technologies.

We do not use cookies, local storage, e-tags, or similar technologies on the Website or Mobile App.

Is my personal information secured?

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect your information, both during transmission and once it is received. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. We and our Service Provider stake appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access or disclosure of the information collected by us. All information collected by Gladiators Software is done so via secured connections and protected and encrypted (using secure socket layer technology, "SSL") by industrial grade security software to guard against unauthorized access.

Contact information.

If you have any questions regarding our Privacy Policy, please use the
